Master...
Your Mandarin is lousy.
It causes my ears discomfort.
You bray like an ass!
You are not to speak unless spoken to.
Is it too much to hope...
you understand Cantonese?
I speak Japanese very well...
I didn't ask if you speak Japanese...
I asked if you understand Cantonese?
You are here to learn the mysteries of
Kung Fu, not linguistics.
If you can't understand me... I will
communicate with you like I would a dog.
When I yell, when I point, when I beat you
with my stick!
Bill is your master, is he not?
Your master tells me...
you're not entirely unschooled.
What training do you possess?
The exquisite art of the Samurai sword.
Don't make me laugh!
Your so-called exquisite art,
is only fit for...
Japanese fat heads!
Your anger amuses me. Do you believe
you are my match?
No.
Are you aware I kill at will?
Yes.
Is it your wish to die?
No.
Then you must be stupid...
Then you must be stupid... so stupid.
Rise, and let me look at your
ridiculous face.
Rise.
So my pathetic friend...
Is there anything that you can do well?
What's the matter?
Cat got your tongue?
- Oh yes, you speak Japanese.
I despise the Goddamn Japs!
Go to that rack.
Remove the sword.
Let's see how good you really are.
If...
...you land a single blow,
I'll bow down and call you master.
From here you can get an excellent
view of my foot.
Your swordsmanship... is amateur at best.
Your so-called kung-fu... is really...
quite pathetic.
I asked you to demonstrate... what you know
- and you did...
Not a goddamn thing!
Let's see your Tiger Crane...
match my Eagle's Claw.
Like all Yankee women...
...all you can do is order in restaurants
and spend a man's money.
Excruciating... isn't it?
Yes!
If it was my wish...
...I could chop your arm off.
It's my arm now. I can do what I please.
If you can stop me... I suggest you try.
I can't.
Because you're helpless?
Yes.
Have you ever felt this before?
No.
Compared to me... you're as helpless
as a worm fighting an eagle?
YES!!!
THAT'S THE BEGINNING!
Is it your wish to possess this
kind of power?
Your training will begin... tomorrow.
Since your arm now belongs to me...
...I want it strong.
Can you do that?
I can, but not that close.
Then you can't do it.
What if your enemy... is three inches
in front of you...
...What do you do then...
...Curl into a ball...
...or do you put your FIST through him?
Now begin.
It's the wood that should fear your hand...
- not the other way around.
No wonder you can't do it... you acquiesce
to defeat... before you even begin.
If you want to eat like a dog...
You can live and sleep outside like a dog.
If you want to live and sleep
like a human...
...pick up those sticks.
Elle, you treacherous dog.
I - give - you - my - word...